{
    "subject": "resource/Hassan_Ghul",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "2012",
    "human_readable": "Hassan Ghul died in 2012.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8048896789550781,
            "question": "When did Hassan Ghul die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7476628422737122,
            "question": "What year was Hassan Ghul's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7384343147277832,
            "question": "Was Hassan Ghul alive in 2013?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846046805381775,
            "question": "Who was Hassan Ghul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40771082043647766,
            "question": "In which decade did Hassan Ghul pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33874499797821045,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Hassan Ghul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33493825793266296,
            "question": "What is known about Hassan Ghul's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3292682468891144,
            "question": "Was Hassan Ghul a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2374935895204544,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Hassan Ghul's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2238546907901764,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Hassan Ghul's work or accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hassan Ghul died in 2012.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2051_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Hassan Ghul's background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2051_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Hassan Ghul a public figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2051_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Hassan Ghul's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2051_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2051_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided confirm that Hassan Ghul was killed by a CIA drone strike in October 2012, supporting the statement that he died in 2012."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information across the provided documents supports that Hassan Ghul died in 2012, specifically mentioning his death in October 2012 due to a CIA drone strike."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}